(Arthur:)Oh, great. This again.
(Sheldon:)Arthur, what brings you back?
Uh, beats me. I-I just...
hope this isn't a-a sex dream.
(Sheldon:)In the past, you've come to me
(Sheldon:)when I'm struggling
with a dilemma.
And-and the one time where...
where you were afraid,
(Arthur:)and you needed me for...
for a night light.
What's-what's troubling you?
(Sheldon:)Well...
(Sheldon:)my friends are telling me
(Sheldon:)I shouldn't abandon
my girlfriend on her birthday
to see the new Star Wars movie.
(Arthur:)Well, sounds right.
(Arthur:)Can... can I get out of this...
(Arthur:)muumuu now?
(Sheldon:)Those are the robes of the Jedi,
(Sheldon:)the guardians of peace
and justice in the galaxy.
And they... they-they don't wear
underwear.